<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blog - xCATTX.COM</title>
	<atom:link href="https://xcattx.com/category/blog/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://xcattx.com</link>
	<description>Awesome Codes for You</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 14:16:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://xcattx.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/xcattx-favicon.png</url>
	<title>Blog - xCATTX.COM</title>
	<link>https://xcattx.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>What is the Best Online Editor to Run Html, CSS &#038; JavaScript Projects.</title>
		<link>https://xcattx.com/what-is-the-best-online-editor-to-run-html-css-javascript-projects/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[AOMIE]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 14:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://xcattx.com/?p=81</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>There are plenty of  text editors available today that you can use to build and run your web projects, now the problem with those text editors is that they require a lot of time to setup. Like you need to open the editor then create a new file, then save the file, then you will &#8230;</p>
<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://xcattx.com/what-is-the-best-online-editor-to-run-html-css-javascript-projects/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">What is the Best Online Editor to Run Html, CSS &#038; JavaScript Projects.</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>
<p>The post <a href="https://xcattx.com/what-is-the-best-online-editor-to-run-html-css-javascript-projects/">What is the Best Online Editor to Run Html, CSS & JavaScript Projects.</a> first appeared on <a href="https://xcattx.com">xCATTX.COM</a>.</p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are plenty of  text editors available today that you can use to build and run your web projects, now the problem with those text editors is that they require a lot of time to setup.</p>
<p>Like you need to open the editor then create a new file, then save the file, then you will need to open the file in a browser. Now this might not seem like a lot of work for some, but believe me.. it is!!</p>
<p>To fix this some big-brain people have created online text editors that you can use to run your html, css, js code online.</p>
<h2>What are Online Text Editors ?</h2>
<p>Online text editors are text editors that run on your web browser and doesn&#8217;t require you to install any software on your computer.</p>
<p>You you can just type the URL of the online text editor and you&#8217;re good to go. You can now copy &amp; paste your code in the text editor and the editor will compile and render the code online.</p>
<h2>What is the Best Online Editor for Web Projects?</h2>
<p>Now if you search on google &#8216;online html, css, js editor&#8217; then you will get hundreds of results, which means hundreds of text editors to choose from.</p>
<p>It will take a lot of time to figure out what to use, what will be better,etc&#8230;that&#8217;s why I have already picked the best text editor for web projects that you will definitely love..</p>
<p>The text editor that I recommend you to use is by Sololearn, which is a website that helps you learn to code.</p>
<p>To access the text editor by Sololearn you can search on google for &#8216;sololearn editor&#8217; or you can click on the link given below which will lead you to the Sololearn editor.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><span style="text-decoration: underline;"><span style="color: #ff00ff;"><a style="color: #ff00ff; text-decoration: underline;" href="https://code.sololearn.com/">https://code.sololearn.com/</a></span></span></p>
<p>After you click on the above link, you will need to choose the language in which you want to code in. Choose &#8216;Web&#8217; if you want to code in html, css and js.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-85" src="https://xcattx.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/pick-coding-language.png" alt="pick-coding-language" width="1280" height="500" /></p>
<p>Now you will be in the text editor where you will get three sections, one for html, one for css and one for js, the last section will be for the output.</p>
<p><img loading="lazy" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-84" src="https://xcattx.com/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/solo-learn-editor.png" alt="solo-learn-editor" width="1280" height="500" /></p>
<p>The input windows can be resized using your mouse and to run the code you will need to click on the run button. Now if you want to save the code then you will need to sign-up for an sololearn account which you can do using google or email.</p>
<h2>Conclusion</h2>
<p>So that is the best text editor out there that you can use to build and run web projects at the same time online without the hassle of local text editors.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p><p>The post <a href="https://xcattx.com/what-is-the-best-online-editor-to-run-html-css-javascript-projects/">What is the Best Online Editor to Run Html, CSS & JavaScript Projects.</a> first appeared on <a href="https://xcattx.com">xCATTX.COM</a>.</p>]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
